Guide to the Arthur Kopit Papers MSS.141
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Projects
  - Roswell Box 1, 1992-1994; 31142040619176 (Box 36)
    "CNN-Don Schmitt UFO Crash at Roswell" VHS
    "UFOs, The Unsolved Mystery" VHS
    "Unexplained Mysteries, UFO sighting army base, England" VHS
    "JFK-Bill Cooper"
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040619176
  - Roswell Box 2, 1992-1994; 31142040619192 (Box 37)
    Research articles and notes, news clippings, correspondence, screenplay copies, drafts and revisions, plot summaries, materials concerning arbitration for credit by the Writers Guild of America(also in previous box), previous screenplays and treatments by Paul Davids and Jeremy Kagan.
    Valdamar Valerian, Matrix II: The Abduction and Manipulation of Humans Using Advanced Technology (Arcturus Book Service: s.l., 1990)
    3 5" floppy disks, each carrying drafts or components of the Roswell script, all labeled as Wordstar 5.0
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040619192
  - Roswell Box 3, 1989-1997; 31142040619200 (Box 38)
    Research articles and notes.
    Keith Thompson, Angels and Aliens: UFOs and the Mythic Imagination (Addison-Wesley Publishing: Reading, Mass., 1991)
    Budd Hopkins, Missing Time (Ballantine Books: New York, 1989)
    The Scarlet Pimpernel (1989-1990)
    Script fragments, transcripts of discussion, correspondence, production schedule, initial contract, advertising information.
    Baroness Orczy, Adventures of the Scarlet Pimpernel (Buccaneer Books: New York, 1985)
    Baroness Emmuska Orczy, The Scarlet Pimpernel (Bantam Books: New York, 1992)
    Baroness Orczy, adapted by Beverly Cross, The Scarlet Pimpernel: A Play (Samuel French: London, 1988)
    "William Cooper Exposes Top Secrets"
    "Roswell Press Conference TV News Reports Rod Serling...."
    "CNN Interview Don Schmitt re: UFO book"
    "Roswell-Smith, Dugger, Knight"
    "Intruders Part 2"
    "Pimpernel Ockrent meeting in NY Feb 4, 5, 6" 2 tapes in env.
    "Nan and Frank and Arthur Act II Pimpernel"
    "Tape 2 Nan Frank, Arthur"
    "Pimpernel Worktape #1 10/89"
    "Pimpernel: conversation with Nan Broglio" 1 micro cassette
    "Frank and Nan" 1 micro cassette
    "Pimpernel 2/7/90" 1 micro cassette
    Note: One large legal-sized photocopy of complete manuscript (by Valdamar Valerian, see above) and small amount of other materials moved to Flat Box 7. These are Roswell materials from previous box.
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040619200
  - The Scientific Process Box 1, 1979-1980; 31142040619705 (Box 39)
    Notebooks, index cards and research and reference books.
    Arthur Koestler, The Thirteenth Tribe (Random House: New York, 1976)
    Howard Blum, Out There: The Government's Secret Quest for Extraterrestrials (Simon and Schuster: New York, 1990)
    William J. Broad, Star Warriors (Simon and Schuster: New York, 1985)
    Michio Kaku, Hyperspace: A Scientific Odyssey Through Parallel Universes, Time Warps, and the Tenth Dimension (Oxford University Press: New York; Oxford, 1994)
    Carlos Castaneda, The Second Ring of Power (Simon and Schuster: New York, 1977)
    Robert Heilbroner, Visions of the Future: The Distant Past, Yesterday, Today, Tomorrow (Oxford University Press: New York; Oxford, 1995)
    David Rorvik, In His Image: The Cloning of a Man (J.B. Lippincott: New York, 1978)
    June Goodfield, Playing God (Random House: New York, 1977)
    Micro Cassettes
    "6/22/79 Scientific Process"
    "Side B: Orano Central Camera Argument 3/10"
    "Nadia" et al. 5 tapes in cardboard box
    "Scientific Progress" et al. 6 tapes in plastic box
    Note: Material is very musty and yellowed but not evidently water damaged or moldy. Two sets of tapes are unfoldered due to size of cases.One folder of sketchbook pages moved to Flat Box 7.
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040619705
  - The Scientific Process Box 2, 31142040619713 (Box 40)
    Stephen Rosen Future Facts (Simon and Schuster: New York, 1976)
    Howard Gardner, The Shattered Mind (Vintage Books: new York, 1974)
    Brett Bolton, Edgar Cayce Speaks (Avon: New York, 1969)
    Alexandra David-Neel, Magic and Mystery in Tibet (Penguin Books: New York, 1978)
    Sir Richard Burton and F.F. Arbuthnot trans., The Kama Sutra of Vatsayana (Panther Books: London, 1963)
    W.Y. Evans-Wentz ed., The Tibetan Book of the Great Liberation (Oxford University Press: New York, 1977)
    Carl Sagan ed., Communication with Extraterrestrial Intelligence (MIT Press: Cambridge, Mass., 1973)
    Daedalus Summer 1967
    Robert S. de Ropp, The New Prometheus (Delta: New York, 1973)
    Steven Rose, The Conscious Man (Vintage Books: New York, 1976)
    Louis E. Rhine, PSI: What is it? (Harper and Row: New York, 1976)
    Brian N. Ball, The Probability Man (Daw Books: New York, 1972)
    William Sears, The Wine of Astonishment (George Ronald: s.l., 1972)
    Jess Stearn, Edgar Cayce: The Sleeping Prophet (Bantam Books: New York, 1971)
    Isaac Asimov, The Genetic Code (Signet Books: New York, 1962)
    Isaac Asimov, Words of Science (Mentor Books: New York, 1959)
    Ted Howard and Jeremy Rifkin, Who Should Play God? (Dell: New York, 1977)
    Gerrit L. Verschuur, Cosmic Catastrophes (Addison-Wesley: Reading, Mass., 1978)
    Arthur C. Clarke, Profiles of the Future (Bantam Books: New York, 1972)
    Louis Pauwels and Jacques Bergier, Impossible Possibilities (Avon: New York, 1973)
    Carl Sagan, The Cosmic Connection (Dell: New York, 1975)
    Robert E. Ornstein, The Psychology of Consciousness (Penguin Books: New York, 1972)
    James D. Watson, The Double Helix (Mentor: New York, 1969)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040619713
  - Secrets of the Rich Box 1, 1976-1977; 31142040619721 (Box 41)
    Scripts and script revisions, all pulled from carefully labeled cartons (retained), fragments and revisions.
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040619721
  - Secrets of the Rich Box 2, 1976-1976; 31142040619739 (Box 42)
    Script fragments and revisions, handwritten notes and drafts, index cards and notebooks.
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040619739
  - The Shroud Box 1, 1979-1987; 31142040619432 (Box 43)
    Road maps, plats, AAA tour guides to Utah, New Mexico, Arizona, and other areas; handwritten notes, typescript screenplay of "The Shroud", manuscript entitled "The Shroud: a Novel", a "treatment for a film" of same, large sketchbook notes and schematics, notebooks, character summations.
    " 'Shroud' Stevenson Talk 12/6/81" 1 micro cassette
    Note: Some photos in folders at end of box interspersed with notes. One folder also of 16 color 35mm slides.
    Note: Two oversized rolls of maps, one legal folder of same with handwritten notes and pages, one folder of contracts and correspondence moved to Flat Box 7; 5 large sketchbooks moved to Flat Box 8.
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040619432
  - The Shroud Box 2, 1980; 31142040619440 (Box 44)
    Copies of the screenplay and treatment, script of the film "The Boys form Brazil", revisions and handwritten edits, index cards,
    "In Search of...The Shroud of Turin" Beta
    "re: The Shroud; John Paul and the Vatican" Beta
    "Center for Disease Control P3 Lab" VHS
    "Shroud" VHS
    "Ken Stevenson on the Shroud 12/6/82"
    "Shroud Lecture"
    Micro Cassettes (in coin env.s)
    "for The Shroud; Strat and Leonie(?) on 'The Ambiguon'" 1 tape
    "Tape of TV show on Shroud by CBN" 1 tape
    "Tom d' Muhala on Long Island" 1 tape
    "March 29, 1980 Tom d' Muhala on L.I." 1 tape
    "Tom d' Muhala 2nd visit" 1 tape
    "McGore's Lab MacGore himself" 3 tapes
    "March 29, 1980 Tom d' Muhala on L.I." 3 tapes
    "Shroud March 21 1980 Tom d' Muhala" 1 tape
    "March 13 #1 Shroud" 1 tape
    "Rockefeller University March 13 1980 #3"1 tape
    "March 13 1980 #2" 1 tape
    "Shroud Rock U. (?)" 1 tape loose
    "Monday March 10 Rockefeller University" 1 tape
    Note: One folder of numerous 35mm slides in sealed white env.s, located immediately behind video tapes. One commercial filmstrip of still images of the Vatican. All images and microcassettes removed from green plastic index card box labeled "tapes: research The Shroud".
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040619440
  - The Shroud Box 3, 1979-1980; 31142040619457 (Box 45)
    Scripts, notes, memos, magazines and research, sketchbooks.
    Robert K. Wilcox, Shroud (Bantam Books: New York, 1978)
    Ian Wilson, The Shroud of Turin (Image Books: New York, 1979)
    "World Within a World--The Maximum Containment Laboratory" Large format video tape
    "Leslie on Cambodians"
    "Leslie on Laotians"
    "Lybians"
    5 tapes labeled 1-3, 6, 8
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040619457
  - The Shroud Box 4, 31142040619473 (Box 46)
    Articles, brochures, research materials, newspapers and news clippings, magazines, draft of film treatment, index cards.
    United States Conference of Research on the Shroud of Turin, Proceedings, March 23-24 1977
    Frank C. Tribbe Portrait of Jesus? (Stein and Day: New York, 1983)
    Peter M. Rinaldi, When Millions Saw the Shroud (Don Bosco: New Rochelle, NY, 1979)
    Thomas Humber, The Sacred Shroud (Pocket Books: New York, 1978)
    Kenneth E. Stevenson and Gary R. Habermas, Verdict on the Shroud (Servant Books: Ann Arbor, Mich., 1981)
    Frank O. Adams, Sindon (Synergy Books: s.l., 1982)
    John Heller, Report on the Shroud of Turin (Houghton Mifflin: Boston, 1983)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040619473
  - The Shroud Box 5, 1981-1992; 31142040619465 (Box 47)
    Magazines, newspapers and clippings, research book lists and bibliographies, book contract extension, notebooks, typed drafts, index cards.
    Geoffrey Ashe, Miracles (Sphere Books: s.l., 1979)
    Edward Abbey, The Journey Home (E.P. Dutton: New York, 1977)
    Arizona Highways Bound volume of 1984 issues
    "Shroud Tapes" 7 tapes in env., 1 empty case
    "Shroud David Newman's Comments" 1 tape in env.
    "re: The Shroud: Random thoughts on side A" 1 tape in env.
    "Shroud Notes March '92" 1 tape in env.
    "20/20 Shroud audio part of video" 1 tape
    "re: Shroud. LG and ALK after Picker conversation" 2 tapes in env.
    "Shroud Lecture Davis, Molander" 1 tape
    "5* Heller" 1 tape
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040619465
  - The Shroud Box 6, ca. 1982-1986; 31142040619507 (Box 48)
    Newspapers, magazines, articles.
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040619507
  - Sweet Smell of Success Box 1, 1994-1995; 31142040619481 (Box 49)
    Handwritten notes, sketches, and ideas, index cards, notebooks, background information provided by Livent, script of "Ragtime", script outline, research, heavily tagged script of film.
    Jan Morris, Manhattan '45 (Oxford University Press: New York, 1987)
    Ernest Lehman, Sweet Smell of Success and Other Stories (s.n.: s.l., s.d.)
    Neal Gabler, Winchell (Knopf: New York, 1994)
    "Walter Winchell" AandE, VHS
    "Winchell" VHS
    "Sweet Smell of Success" original movie, VHS
    "Notes on SS of S Aug '94"
    "Cy Coleman's House #1"
    "Cy Susan and Arthur review"
    "Cy Coleman, 6/23, SSofS" 1 micro cassette.
    Note: 2 folders of large sketchbook pages moved to Flat Box 8.
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040619481
  - Till Death Us Do Part Box 1, 1988-1989; 31142040619515 (Box 50)
    Based on work by Vincent Bugliosi. Includes portions of Bugliosi's book, notes, index cards, drafts, revisions, draft fragments, notebooks.
    Vincent Bugliosi, Till Death Us Do Part (Bantam Books: New York, 1979)
    "Gary Hoffman phone call" 1 micro cassette in env.
  - Till Death Us Do Part Box 2, 1988-1989; 31142040619499 (Box 51)
    Portions of the book, copious index cards, notebooks, letter from Bugliosi, handwritten notes.
    Note: Small amount of oversized sketchbook pages moved to Flat Box 9.
  - Treasure Island Box 1, 1993-1994; 31142040619531 (Box 52)
    Magazines and pamphlets on diving, reprints of 19th and early 20th century books on pirates, notebooks, script drafts, fragments and revisions, correspondence, handwritten notes and index cards.
    Howard Pyle, The Buccaneers and Marooners of America (Rio Grande Press: Glorietta, N.M., 1990)
    Philip Gosse, The History of Piracy (Rio Grande Press: Glorietta, N.M., 1990)
    Ralph D. Paine, The Book of Pirate Treasures (Rio Grande Press: Glorietta, N.M., 1992)
    Robert Williams, Memoirs of a Buccaneer (Rio Grande Press: Glorietta, N.M., 1990)
    Harold T. Wilkins, Treasure Hunting (Rio Grande Press: Glorietta, N.M., 1989)
    Esquemeling, The Buccaneers of America (Rio Grande Press: Glorietta, N.M., 1992)
    A. Hyatt Verrill, In the Wake of the Buccaneers (Rio Grande Press: Glorietta, N.M., 1990)
    Charles Ellms, The Pirates' Own Book(Rio Grande Press: Glorietta, N.M., 1993)
    John Huber, Joyce Huber, and Christopher Lofting, Best Dives of the Western Hemisphere (Hunter Publishing: Edison, N.J., 1990)
    "Raising the Titanic" VHS
    "Tape of my meeting...with Mark Ovitz and Glen Carron" 1 micro cassette in env.
    "Treasure Island Dec '93"
    6 tapes if meeting with Mark Ovitz in L.A.3/14-3/15/94
    Note: One folder of oversized material moved to Flat Box 9.
  - Treasure Island Box 2, 1993-1995; 31142040619523 (Box 53)
    Pamphlets, magazines, articles, research correspondence, all on diving, sunken treasure and pirates, modern and historical, screenplay drafts.
    Galleon Explorers Club, Spanish Treasure, A VHS tape and one audio tape in case.
    Academy of Marine Sciences and Undersea research, Who's Who in Scuba Diving (Best Publishing: Flagstaff, Ariz., 1992)
    John Halas, Judy Halas and Don Kincaid, Diving and Snorkeling Guide to the Florida Keys (Pisces Books: Houston, 1984)
    Steve Blount and Lisa Walker, Treasure Hunting with a Metal Detector (Pisces Books: Glen Cove, N.Y.,1987)
    Jeppesen Sanderson, Inc., Open Water Sport Diver Manual (s.n.: s.l., 1984)
    Gary Gentile, Ultimate Wreck Diving Guide (Gary Gentile Productions: Philadelphia, 1992)
    1 tape, see above
    "Conversation with Herwitz re: Treasure Island"
    1 VHS tape, see above.
    Note: Two legal pads moved to Flat Box 9.
  - Treasure Island Box 3, 1992; 31142040619556 (Box 54)
    Research materials, notes, notebooks, expenses and receipts from travel, pamphlets, maps, books.
    Rebecca L. Johnson, Diving into Darkness (Lerner Publications: Minneapolis, Minn., 1989)
    Philip Gosse, The Pirates' Who's Who (Rio Grande Press: Glorieta, N.M., 1988)
    Kal Muller, Spice Islands: Exotic eastern Asia (Passport Books: Lincolnwood, Ill., 1993)
    Steve Blount, Diving and Snorkeling Guide to the Bahamas, Nassau and New Providence Island (Pisces Books: Locust Valley, N.Y., 1985)
    Denise Berg and Daniel Berg, Tropical Shipwrecks (Aqua Explorers: New York, 1989)
    Jennifer Marx, Pirates and Privateers of the Caribbean (Krieger Publishing: Malabar, Flor., 1992)
    A. Hyatt Verrill, The Real Story of the Pirate (Rio Grande Press: Glorieta, N.M., 1989)
    Robert Louis Stevenson, Treasure Island (Charles Scribner's Sons: New York, 1981)
    Paul Woods, Kristiana Sarwo Rini and Margit Meinhold, Indonesian Phrasebook (Lonely Planet: Hawthorne, Australia, 1992)
    David Cordingly and John Falconer, Pirates Fact and Fiction (Artebras: New York, 1992)
    Colin Sheaf and Richard Kilburn, The Hatcher Porcelain Cargoes (Phaidon: Oxford, 1988)
    Douglas Botting, The Pirates (Time-Life Books: Alexandria, Virg., 1978)
    Bradley Sheard, Beyond Sportdiving! (Menasha Ridge Press: Birmingham, Ala., 1991)
    Glenn Caron #1 Nov. 28"
    "Glenn Caron #2
    Note: Many books heavily tagged. One audio tape needs case. 3 legal note pads and oversized sheets moved to Flat Box 9.
  - Treasure Island Box 4, 1992-1994; 31142040619549 (Box 55)
    Magazines, pamphlets, books, tapes, brochures, maps, drafts of screenplay.
    Birnbaum's 94 Bahamas and Turks and Caicos (HarperPerennial: New York, 1993)
    John S. Potter, Jr., The Treasure Diver's Guide (Florida Classics Library: Port Sakerno, Fla., 1988)
    Alan R. Rowe, Relics, Water and the Kitchen Sink (Sea Sports Publications: Norwalk, Conn., 1979)
    Fodor's 94 Caribbean (Fodor's Travel Publications: New York, 1993)
    Hans Johannes Hoefer, Philippines (APA Publications: Hong Kong, 1991)
    Shlomo Cohen and Roni Cohen, Cayman Diver's Guide (Seapen Books: Tel-Aviv, 1991)
    "Conversation with Alex re: Draft 2 12/27/94"
    "Alex's Comments re: Tr. Isl. Draft 2"
    "Alex and ALK in car 9/11/93"
    "Bob Marx and helicopters 11/4/93"
    "Bob Marx at JFK"
    "9/15-9/16 L.A....with Mark Ovitz"
    "Last Day in L.A.--Recap with Mark Ovitz"
    "Phone Calls"
    "Treasure Island second evening"
    "Bob and Jennifer Marx part I"
    "Bob Marx Part II"
    "Robert Baer Part I"
    9 tapes in two cases, variously marked, Fall '93
    "Treasure Island Tape #3"
    "Pimpernel #3"
    "Treasure Island Alex Tape" 1 tape in env.
    "Tr. Island Conversation with Alex...9/3/94" 2 tapes in env.
    Note: Oversized maps, posters and notes moved to Flat Box 9.
  - Treasure Island Box 5, 31142040619572 (Box 56)
    Magazines, brochures and other publications along with some schedule and planning notes on the Caribbean, the Cayman Islands, Key West and other tropical locations.
  - Treasure Island Box 6, 31142040619564 (Box 57)
    Magazines, pamphlets, audio and video tapes, books, maps and notes.
    Eric Oey, ed., Java: Garden of the East (Passport Books: Lincolnwood, Ill., 1991)
    Robert F. Marx, Shipwrecks in the Americas (Dover Publications: New York, 1987)
    ----, The Underwater Dig: Introduction to Marine Archaeology (Pisces Books: Houston, 1990)
    Philip S. Olin, Treasure: The Business and Technology (The Printing Division of Mr. Paper: Gainesville, Fla., 1991)
    Robert F. Marx with Jennifer Marx, In Quest of the Great White Gods (Crown Publishers: New York, 1992) Inscribed by the author
    Cathie Drane and Barbara Hall, Culture Shock: Indonesia (Graphic Arts Publishing Company: Portland, Ore., 1993)
    Kal Muller Underwater Indonesia (Passport Books: Lincolnwood, Ill., 1992)
    Kal Muller, East of Bali: From Lombok to Timor (Passport Books: Lincolnwood, Ill., 1991)
    All tapes are VHS
    "Quest for Gold"
    "Bali"
    "Malaysia"
    "National Geographic: Atocha, Quest for Treasure"
    "Singapore--Part I"
    "Sand and Sea, Treasure of Indian Ocean"
    "The Treasure Experience"
    "Atlantis Research Submersibles
    "The Deep"
    "Peak Performance Buoyancy"
    "Nanking Cargo"
    "Treasure Island Disney 1851"
    "Treasure: What Dreams are Made of..."
    "James Bond underwater sequence"
    "Kopit"
    "Treasure Island w;/ Wallace Beery" 2 tapes
    "Carl Fismer's Treasure Hunting Made Easy"
    "Caymans"
    "Key West--Jupiter--Sebastian"
    "? Latter part, end of deep submersible"
    "Treasure Island Tapes #1,2,3" 3 microcassettes in two env.s
    "Dr. Hamilton Tape"
  - Wings Box 1, 1976-1978; 31142040619598 (Box 58)
    Production scripts and other scripts and script fragments, French adaptation of Wings (undated), handwritten notes and notebooks, much apparently from the production of the Yale Repertory Theater, design and layout of playbill, production contract between Roger L. Stevens and Kopit, and Yale and Kopit, galleys of publication of play.
    "Nancy Darboun and Jacqueline Doolittle discussing Wings" 2 tapes with same label
    unlabeled tape without case
    "demo tape for earplay various persons talking--Laura Killian"
    "Earplay '76 demo tape"
    Note: One oversized (approx 11x17") production script to separate out.
  - Wings Box 2, 1979-1993; 31142040619580 (Box 59)
    Material including drafts of screenplay, correspondence, notebook relating to 1991 production in L.A. or also a Hallmark television version of the play. Contract, notes, correspondence, for 1980 "American Playhouse" television production. Contract for National Theater (Eng.) production, Farrar Strauss publication galleys, layout. News clippings, corrected proofs of Samuel French edition, radio script of Wings for Earplay, as originally commissioned. 1983 screenplay draft, index cards and heavily annotated copy of screenplay.
    A.R. Luria, The Working Brain (Basic Books: New York, 1973)
    "Wings Jacqui Doolittle...conversation at Livero's Restaurant" 2 tapes in env.
    "Wings conversation with Doolittle 4/28/91" 1 tape in env.
    "Wings Jacqui Doolittle Tape #2" 1 tape in env.
    "Wings 3/92" 1 tape in env.
    "Wings--Friday night April 5th" 1 tape in env.
    "May (O'Neill)
    "no. 2 Bert Leonard"
    "12/5"
    "Secrets at MacDonell"
    1 unlabeled tape
    "Jacqui Doolittle"
    "Jacqui Doolittle Monday March 25, 1991"
    "Jacqui Doolittle on phone March 25, 1991"
    The following tapes were found in a single cigar box
    "Aphasic demo tape"
    tapes labeled #3-7, 9, 10
    empty tape case labeled #2
    "Th. Feigerson and Jacqui Doolittle"
    "Wings at Burke"
    The following tapes were found in a bag
    Wings comments and conversation with Joe Broido, 3 tapes
    Note: 1 folder of oversized material moved to Flat Box 9; 3 folders of oversized material moved to Flat Box 10
  - Wings Box 3, 1990-1991; 31142040620018 (Box 60)
    Drafts and revisions of the Hallmark production, index cards, large sketch pages, discussion and interview transcripts, news clippings, correspondence, research, notebooks.
    "Wings 5/10/91" 1 tape in env.
    "Wings--L.A.conversation" 4 tapes in env.
    "Jacqui and Dr. Caravelli 5/11/90....." 2 tapes in env.
    "Rhinebeck air show"
    Note: Stack of snapshots of air show at back of box. 1 folder of oversized material moved to Flat Box 10.
  - Wings Box 4, 1978-1991; 31142040619606 (Box 61)
    More material from unproduced Hallmark teleplay, drafts and draft fragments, notebooks, news articles and research. The following material was removed from two brown cardboard file boxes: press releases, articles and reviews of Wings in its initial Broadway run, programs, correspondence concerning regional productions, magazines. Also found are two copies of script by Kopit: "Starstruck or Pie in the Sky" of unknown date.
    Arthur Kopit, Wings (Hill and Wang: New York, 1978)
    Arthur Kopit, Wings: A Drama (Samuel French: New York, 1978)
    Franz Rottensteiner, The Science Fiction Book (New American Library: New York, 1975)
  - Norman in Wonderland Box 1, 1991-1992; 31142040620059 (Box 62)
    Subtitled "Good News/Bad News". Scripts and script fragments, information, articles, magazines and correspondence on soap operas, notebooks and handwritten notes, scripts of episodes of "Northern Exposure", note pads.
    "Northern Exposure" episodes 78701 and 78703, 2 VHS tapes
    In env.s
    "Phone call re: soap...July 1, 1991" 1 tape
    "Leslie and Arthur...about the suicide of Mr. Moe(?)" 1 tape
    "Soap--Brooklyn NBC 'Another World'" 1 tape
    "5/14/91...Comments on my script to 'Another World'" 1 tape
    Loose
    "Soap July 1991
    "Norman in Wonderland Oct 3, 1991"
    "Norman in Wonderland Oct 31, 1991"
    "Kate's Tape Diary"
    "CBS Soap July 31st conversation with Leslie"
    "LA trip July 23, 1991"
    "Ben on complex numbers" no case
    "Dalton 8/1/92 Arthur 8/1/92"
    Jennifer Alwood re: soap"
    "CBS soap pilot...8/23/91" 2 tapes in env.
    "'Guiding Light'...9/11/91" 2 tapes in env.
    Note: One folder of oversized material moved to Flat Box 10.
  - Norman in Wonderland Box 2, 1991-1996; 31142040620042 (Box 63)
    Articles, news clippings, notepad, notebooks.
    "Wonderland Feb '96"
    "...Feb '96 Wonderland" 1 tape in env.
    "Cheeky Peeky and Zhivago (late 2000)"
    "Transcribe this Wonderland history of Brock's Party"
    "Wonderland (CA) 2/26 etc." 2 tapes in case
    Note: Box is less than half full and will fit into Ms. box.
  - Zhivago, 1998; 31142040620067 (Box 64)
    Correspondence, typescript and handwritten drafts and fragments, research, lyrics, schedules of activity, plot schematics.
    Note: Oversized folders moved to Flat Box 10